Guide to the Rochambeau Papers and Rochambeau Family Cartographic Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 35; (15 boxes)
  - BROADSIDE CASE
    - Series V. Map Collection of the Comte de Rochambeau
      - War of the Austrian Succession: Low Countries Campaign
        - IK 117 Environs of Béthune, Douai, etc. Paris: Crépy., 1743 (Box 49, Folder 836)
        - IK 90 Low Countries: Brabant. Paris: Crépy., 1744 (Box 49, Folder 837)
        - IK 143 Environs of Liège, Maastricht, etc. Paris: Crépy., 1744 (Box 49, Folder 838)
        - IK 167 The Palatinate and Electorate of the Rhine. Paris: Crépy. (Box 49, Folder 839)
        - IK 214 The Electorate of Mayence. Paris: Le Rouge., 1742 (Box 49, Folder 840)
        - IK 86 Lille and Tournai. Paris: Le Rouge., 1744 (Box 49, Folder 841)
        - IK 89 Environs of Venlo, etc. Paris., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 842)
      - Cantons of Franche-Comté and Campaign Against Mandrin
        - IK 66 Map of Franche-Comté. Paris: Jean Querret., 1748 (Box 49, Folder 843-846)
      - Seven Years' War: German Campaign
        - IK 188 Plan of Wesel. Paris: Le Rouge., 1757 (Box 49, Folder 847)
        - IK 145, Nos. 1-6 Theater of War in Germany. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1769 (Box 49, Folder 848-853)
        - IK 145 No. 10 Plan of the Army's Movements from May 26-30 and Aug-Sep 1758. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1766 (Box 49, Folder 854)
        - IK 145 No. 15 Sangershausen and Lutternberg. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1766 (Box 49, Folder 855)
        - IK 145 No. 18 Battle of Tonhausen. The Hague., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 856)
        - IK 145 No. 19 Battle of Vellinghausen. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1762 (Box 49, Folder 857)
        - IK 145 No. 20 Siege of Brunswick. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1763 (Box 49, Folder 858)
        - IK 145 No. 22 Siege of Cassel. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1763 (Box 49, Folder 859)
        - IK 145 No. 23 Siege of Minden. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1766 (Box 49, Folder 860)
        - IK 145 No. 24 Plan of the Crossing of the Aller. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1765 (Box 49, Folder 861)
        - IK 205bis. Southern Part of the Hanoverian Electorate. Paris., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 862)
        - IK 208 Hanover. Paris: Le Rouge., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 863)
        - IK 168 Plan of Kassel. Strasbourg., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 864)
      - Inspector-General of Infantry
        - IK 76-81 The States of Lorraine. Alexis Hubert Jaillot., 1743, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 865-870)
      - Plan to Invade England
        - IK 327 Small English Sea Chart. Paris: Jean Lattré., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 871)
        - IK 330 Islands of Jersey and Guernsey. Paris: Jean Lattré. (Box 49, Folder 872)
        - IK 322 The Provinces of the Low Countries. Paris: Eugene Henry Friex., 1744 (Box 49, Folder 873)
        - IK 57 Brittany Divided in Nine Dioceses. Paris: Alexis Hubert Jaillot., 1706 (Box 49, Folder 874)
      - Command of Picardy and Artois
        - IK 96 Provinces of Picardy and Artois, by Jean B. Nolin. Paris: Basset., 1785 (Box 49, Folder 875)
        - IK 60 Topographical map of Cherbourg by Jean B. Nolin., 1787 (Box 49, Folder 876)
        - IK 61 Map of Cherbourg., 1786 (Box 49, Folder 877)
        - IK 129 Holland. Matthaeus Seutter. (Box 49, Folder 878)
        - IK 116 Environs of Dunkerque, Gravelines and Saint Omer. Paris: Crépy. (Box 49, Folder 879)
        - IK 107 Environs of Kortrijk, Audenaarde, Mons. Paris: Crépy., 1743 (Box 49, Folder 880)
        - IK 34bis Plan of Rochefort. Paris., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 881)
      - Command of Alsace
        - IK 71 Alsace. Matthaeus Seutter., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 882)
      - Journey to Switzerland
        - IK 306 Switzerland. Paris: Jean B. Nolin., 1746 (Box 49, Folder 883)
      - Army of the North: Brabant Campaign
        - IK 91 United Provinces of the Low Countries. Paris: Basset., 1785 (Box 49, Folder 884)
        - IK 95 Map of Flanders. Paris: Basset., 1790 (Box 49, Folder 885)
        - IK 40 France Divided Into 85 Departments. Paris: Desnos., 1792 (Box 49, Folder 886)
    - Series VI. Map Collection of the Vicomte de Rochambeau
      - IK 391 The Antilles. Paris., 1775
      - Italian Campaign and Command of Liguria
        - IK 277 The States of Savoy and Piedmont. Paris: Jean B. Nolin., 1742 (Box 49, Folder 888)
      - Russian Campaign
        - IK 339 Russia and Europe by P. F. Tardieu., 1812 (Box 49, Folder 889-891)
  - ROLLED MAPS
    - Series IV. Map Collection of the Marquis de Rochambeau
      Miscellaneous Maps
      - IK 320 Plan of the Siege of Barcelona. Paris., 1698
      - IK 350 Plan of Herakleion. Paris: Alexis Hubert Jaillot., 1669 (Box 49, Folder 893)
    - Series V. Map Collection of the Comte de Rochambeau
      - IK 154 The Area surrounding the Rhine below Speyer near Mayence. Nuremberg: Homann Erben.
      - Low Countries Campaign
        - IK 87 The Counties of Hainaut and Namur. Paris: Crépy., 1744 (Box 49, Folder 895)
      - Seven Years' War: German Campaign
        - IK 145 No. 21 Battle of Wilhelmsthal. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1763 (Box 49, Folder 896)
        - IK 176 Plan of the Affair of Soest. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1766 (Box 49, Folder 897)
        - IK 177 Plan of the Battle of Wilhelmshaven. The Hague: Pierre Gosse, Jr. and Daniel Pinet., 1763 (Box 49, Folder 898)
      - American Revolution
        - IK 351 Map of the Indies by D'Anville., 1752 (Box 49, Folder 899-900)
      - Command of Alsace
        - IK 74 Strasbourg., 1760 (Box 49, Folder 901)
    - Series VI. Map Collection of the Vicomte de Rochambeau
      Italian Campaign and Command of Liguria
      - IK 260bis The Course of the Po, by Placide. Paris: Berey., 1703
      - Spanish and Portugese Campaigns
        - IK 312 Map of Spain and Portugal. Paris., 1823 (Box 49, Folder 903)